eventrebels.com 2008-06-22

# EventRebels.com - The Online-Onsite Registration Company

EventRebels is committed to protecting the privacy of our users' personally identifiable information. To better protect the privacy of meeting or event registrants and of our clients (meeting planners), we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices users can make about the way their information is used at the site. 

## Information Collection and Use

### Personally Identifiable Information 

#### A. Registrants

Where registrants sign up to participate in an event, we collect certain personally identifiable information on behalf of the meeting planner to enable them to participate. The types of personally identifiable information we collect on behalf of the meeting planner may include: name, address, telephone number, e-mail address, credit card information, type and size of the business, and other similar demographic information. 

Meeting planners may use this information for such purposes as to process your registration requests, to communicate with you about events that they are offering, for example, to send you invitations, confirmations, reminders and general information about events in which are or be may interested, as well as to enable you to manage your registration data (e.g., to enable you to register, update or cancel a reservation). EventRebels uses your personally identifiable information only to provide the meeting planners with the services they have contracted us for. EventRebels' privacy policy does not cover the meeting planner's use of your information. For more information on how your information is used by the meeting planner of an event for which you register, consult the individual privacy policy of your meeting planner. 

In some instances, EventRebels may collect credit card information to enable users to sign up for meeting planners' events. Where we collect this information, we use it only for the purposes of processing registrants' requests. 

EventRebels may use registrant information in the aggregate to help improve the content of our Web sites as well as to improve the products and services that we offer to both meeting planners and registrants. 

#### B. Meeting Planners 

To enable meeting planners to take full advantage of our offerings, we collect certain information when these users request information from our site. The types of personally identifiable information we collect may include: name, address, telephone number, e-mail address, and type of business. 

We use this information to communicate with them about their account with us and process their requests for our products and services, as well as to provide them with opportunities to purchase products or services in which they may be interested. 

We also collect name and e-mail address from meeting planners to enable them to sign up for our newsletter. If, at any time, you no longer wish to receive these newsletters, simply unsubscribe by following the instructions that appear in the newsletter, or sending us an e-mail at info@eventrebels.com 

### Non-Personally Identifiable Information 

We may collect certain non-personally identifiable information about our users when they visit many of our web pages such as the type of browser you are using (e.g., Netscape, Internet Explorer), the type of operating system they are using (e.g., Windows '98 or Mac OS), and the domain name of their Internet service provider (e.g., America Online, Earthlink). 

We use the non-personally identifiable information that we collect to improve the design and content of our site and to enable us to personalize users' Internet experience. We also may use this information in the aggregate to analyze site usage, as well as to offer products or services. 

### Legal Process and Corporate Restructuring

We may disclose personally identifiable information in response to legal process or when we believe in good faith that the law requires it, for example, in response to a court order, subpoena, or a law enforcement agency's request. In addition, in the event that all or substantially all of EventRebel's stock and/or assets are transferred or sold to another entity, EventRebels may transfer such information to the acquiring entity. 

## Choices/Opt-Out

EventRebels may contact meeting planners to provide them with opportunities to purchase products or services that may be of interest to them. If meeting planners prefer not to receive marketing information from this site, just let us know by sending us an e-mail at privacy@eventrebels.com. 

[We also may share meeting planners' personally identifiable information with select third parties to enable them to learn about other products or services that may be of interest to them. If meeting planners prefer not to receive marketing information from these third parties, just let us know by sending us an e-mail at privacy@eventrebels.com. 

## Cookies

EventRebels uses "cookies" to enhance users experience with our site. Cookies are text files we place in a user's computer's browsers to store your preferences. We cannot use our cookies to determine any personally identifiable information about users. 

We use cookies to understand site usage, to personalize users' experience, and to improve the content and offerings on our site. For example, we may use cookies to personalize users' experience at our Web pages (e.g., to recognize you by name when you return to our site) and save password in password-protected areas. 

## Collection of Information by Others

Our site contains links to other Web sites whose information practices may be different than ours. Users should consult the other sites' privacy notices, as we have no control over information that is submitted to, or collected by, these third parties. 

We sometimes may offer promotions that are sponsored by, or co-branded with, identified third parties. By virtue of these relationships, the third parties may obtain personally identifiable information that visitors voluntarily submit to participate in the site activity. EventRebels has no control over the third parties' use of this information. We will notify users if these third parties will obtain such information. 

## Security

We have appropriate security measures in place to prevent against unauthorized access to information that we collect online. In addition, we use encryption technologies when transferring and receiving certain sensitive information (e.g., credit card information) exchanged with our site. 

## Reviewing and Updating Your Information

If event planners would like to review the personally identifiable information we have collected about them online that we maintain, they may do so by choosing "My Profile" from the "Admin" menu of the application or by sending an email request to us at privacy@eventrebels.com. 

Registrants can change or update the registration information that we maintain about them. To do so, they can simply log into their account (by choosing "Update Info" from the event Web site menu) and edit their information accordingly, or by sending an email request to us at privacy@eventrebels.com. 

## Contact Us

If you have any questions regarding this statement, or would like more information on our privacy practices, please contact us at info@eventrebels.com.
